我从"不到一元店"买来的新床单
My new sheets from the "Under a dollar" store
好有奢华风
feel so luxurious,
感觉价值超过一元
like they could maybe cost over a dollar,
值个两到三元呢
maybe even 2 or 3.
对啊 今天在那店真是走运
Yup. It was a good day over at the "Under a dollar."
买到牛排 床品 还有我的吃牛排专座
Steak, bed stuff, and my new steak eatin' chair.
那块肉跟椅子的价格不让你担心吗
Doesn't it worry you that you got that meat and furniture
价钱跟愤怒小鸟软件升级一样呢[一块钱]
for the price of an Angry Birds update?
我可担心这种好事以后碰不上了
Yeah, it worries me that it'll never happen again.
床罩加牛排 以前想都不敢想
Sheets and steak? Never dared to dream it.
这床罩真好闻
These sheets smell amazing too,
都要感谢那一颗要价不到一块钱的
thanks to that one little fabric softener ball,
衣物柔顺球
also under a dollar.
我也跟"一颗球[蛋]"的男人约会过
I dated a guy with one ball once.
他一直很在意 但我告诉他
He was all self-conscious, but I told him,
"别担心 一粒跟两粒一样恶心"
"No big deal. It's just as ugly as two."
我今晚一定能睡一个好...
I am going to get such a good night's--
我的床罩[操]
Oh, sheet!
"织物密度 有
"Thread count: Yes.
洗涤注意事项 不能洗"
Washing instructions: Do not wash."
你确定你要坐那椅子吗
Are you sure you want to sit in that?
臭婆娘 老子吃牛排时 少跟我唧唧歪歪
Woman, don't talk to me while I'm eatin' my steak!
"使用说明 请勿坐"
"Instructions: Do not sit."
沙士桶糖
Yay, root beer barrel!
什么 有糖果指路
What? A candy trail.
神啊 你终于要眷顾我了吗
God, are you just getting to me now?
你显示神迹的方式果然独特啊
You do work in mysterious ways.
我不是神 但我昨晚
I'm not God, but I believe
的确有满足你室友祈祷的愿望
I did answer your roommate's prayers last night.
安迪
Andy!
这是怎么回事
So how'd this happen?
你们怎么重新勾搭上的
Where'd you guys find each other again?
再合网吗
Rematch.Com?
还是空虚阴部佳缘网
Empty-vajay date?
昨晚我就想
No, last night, I thought,
"反正床单都毁[乱]了
"well, these sheets are already ruined,
那好歹也该来一炮来真正弄乱它吧
so I might as well really ruin them with sex,"
所以我就打给安迪啦
so I called Andy.
接到电话 我受宠若惊 就来啦
And I was obviously flattered, so I came over.
希望你们用的是超过一元的套套
Well, I hope you guys spent more than $1 for condoms.
在两种东西上 我从来不省钱
Hey, there are two things I never skimp on:
套套与糖果
condoms and candy.
麦克斯 你有看到我在厨房桌上
And Max, did you see what I left over there
留给你的礼物吗
on the kitchen counter for you?
套套还是糖果 还是装满糖果的套套
Condoms? Candy? Condoms full of candy?
你期望值这么高 那这下要失望了
Well, now, you're going to be disappointed,
因为礼物只有糖果
because it's just candy.
都是我的最爱
Ooh, all my favorites!
我好奇是否在早餐前 我就染会上糖尿病
I wonder if I can get diabetes before breakfast.
谢啦 安迪
Thanks, Andy.
那个糖果是为了调虎离山
That candy was just a decoy,
这样我下床就不会让你看见我的"口红糖"[鸡鸡]
so you didn't see my push pop when I got out of bed.
你跟安迪又好上啦
So...are you and Andy back together?
才没有 只单纯来一炮而已
No. It was just a one-time thing.
瞧你这样
Look at you.
看起来像希腊的约炮女神
You're like the greek goddess of booty calls.
阿芙洛白罩
Aphro-whitey.
好自豪啊 我的第一次约炮
Kind of proud of myself. My very first booty call.
其实还是网上约炮
Well, actually, it was a booty tweet.
约炮也得约得时尚啊
Booty's up with the times.
基本上约炮这事
Technically, booty call's been around
几百年前就有了好吗
since the old-timey times.
发明电话的贝尔打的
Alexander Graham bell's
第一通电话就说"你还醒着呢"[经典约炮金句]
very first phone call was "Hey, you up?"
我得走了 没问题吧
Hey, so, um, I gotta go. Is that cool?
当然没问题 走吧
Oh, super cool, sure.
我们该怎么做 亲一个 还是击个掌
What do we do, kiss? High-five?
麦克斯 你这种时候都怎么做的
Max, what do you do in this situation?
我通常都夹着手臂跟他挥手道别
I usually wave at him with my arm clenched,
因为我藏着他的钱包呢
'cause I'm hiding his wallet in it.
很高兴见到你
Well, nice seeing you.
我通常不会敬礼啦
I don't usually do the salute,
但也没事 能当你的招牌动作
but okay, that can be your thing.
厄尔 这是我最后一张单
Earl, here's my last check.
能帮我结了吗 我准备打电话约炮
Can you tip me out? I have a possible booty call.
卡洛琳
Well, Caroline,
你做这事 让我俩之间又更相近了
you've reached a new place of familiarity with me.
只可惜我不是跟你一起"做"这事
Unfortunately, I've not reached that same place with you.
你能照看一下我这区吗
Can you cover my tables?
打从你第一天来上班 我就在帮你了
I've been doing that since you started working here,
所以没问题
so yes.
那就好 我要发短信给安迪
Good, 'cause I'm gonna text Andy
跟他再约次炮 这次说不定
for another booty call, and maybe this time
我们可以共进个炮后早餐呢
we can go out and have a booty breakfast.
作为约炮地区自治协会的会长呢
As the president of the casual sex society, local chapter,
我认为你假约炮真谈情
I call bull on your booty.
哪有 只是约炮啊
What? It's a booty call.
约你个大头鬼啊
Not with you it isn't.
你想着吃完炮后早餐
You think that booty breakfast
就能约个炮后晚餐
will maybe lead to a booty dinner
接着就炮后订婚 然后炮后结婚
then maybe booty engaged and booty married
生几个炮后娃 再一起搬进炮后老人院
and have a couple booty kids and a booty retirement home
最后炮后一起死
and then booty die together.
才不会呢 他绝对会比我先死
That's not true. He'll die before me,
然后我再去舞蹈班钓男人
then I'll take a dance class.
你在干嘛 想尿尿吗
What are you doing? Do you have to pee?
不是 我感觉下面... 有古怪
No, I feel something... down there.
废话 "她"现在觉醒了 "饥渴"着呢
Yeah, you woke it up. Now it's hungry.
但你不可以带她去吃"同一家餐厅的鸡"哦
But you don't take it back to the same restaunt.
干嘛穿成这样 还系个领结
What is that and why is it wearing a bow tie?
他如果系个普通领带 会垂到地上吧
Maybe because actual tie would drag on the ground.
要说"垂到地上"[地面上拖]
Speaking of "Dragging on the ground,"
你何不去拖一只羚羊回你的淫窝
maybe you could drag an antelope back to your cave
然后跟它爽一下呢
and have sex with it.
你看 我也是个幽默的人
See, I have a sense of humor too.
我交友网站上的个人档案就有写这一特质
That's one of the attributes on my online dating profile.
阿憨 你打扮这么帅是因为要见女孩吗
Han, are you all dressed up because you're expecting a date?
我希望不只是单纯见一下那么简单
Oh, I'm expecting a lot more than a date.
我们的个人档案十分般配
Our profiles matched us perfectly.
-可能就是她了 -哪个她
- This might be the one. - Which one?
你的第一个她 还是唯一那个她
The first one? The only one?
还是不小心踩扁你的那个她
The one that accidentally steps on you?
她半小时前就该到了
She was supposed to be here a half hour ago.
你懂的 地铁总是晚到
Well, you know, subways run late,
尤其是人家根本没上去
especially if you don't get on them
因为那人根本不存在
because you don't really exist
只是个网上骗钱的而已
in our money-scamming man in Nairobi.
您好 我想找老板 李憨先生
Hi, I'm looking for Han Lee, the owner.
她来了 漂亮 金发
There she is. Pretty, blonde,
而且明显不是男人
and clearly not a man.
现在谁爽啊
Who's laughing now?
别太急着下定论
You shouldn't jump to conclusions.
我也曾经跟一个金发美女约过会
I once had a date with a blonde woman.
结果我跟他的共同点 就是都有鸡鸡
Turns out, the curtains matched the penis on that one.
你好 你是艾希莉吗 我是李憨
Hello. Are you Ashley? I'm Han Lee.
你好 幸会幸会
Hi. Nice to meet you.
我有东西忘车上了 马上回来
I left something in my car I'll be right back.
她会回来吗
Is she coming back?
阿憨 耶稣回来人间救赎都比她快
Han, Jesus is coming back before she is.
阿憨 她配不上你
Han, you're too good for her.
我就不懂了
I don't understand.
网站显示我们9成7相配呢
We were 97% compatible on the website.
让我看看你的个人档案
Let me see your profile.
-这头像是谁 -我啊
- Who's that? - That's me.
屁咧 这明明是《天堂执法者》里的亚洲帅哥
No, that's the hot asian star from Hawaii Five-0.
干嘛 我们有点像好吗
What? We kinda look alike.
你们俩唯一相像的地方只有
The only thing you have in common
人家是《夏威夷5-0》[直译]
with this guy from Hawaii five-0
而你是5尺0寸
is that you are 5'0".
阿憨 你还填"运动型"啊
And Han, "athletic"?
我以前是田径铁人呢
In school, I ran track.
从跨栏下方跑过不算是田径好吗
Running under the hurdles doesn't count as track.
阿憨 你这弱爆了
Han, this is totally lame.
让我帮你找个适合你的姑娘吧
Let me help you find the right girl.
你让我建筑无数快乐在你痛苦上
You give me so much joy at your expense,
我觉得我该报答你
I feel like I need to give back.
谢谢你啊 麦克斯
Thank you, Max,
让我受辱之余还能倍感光荣
I'm insulted and honored at the same time.
看到阿憨与艾希莉相会的那一秒
Seeing Han and Ashley together for that one second
让我发觉我想要一段感情
made me realize I want to be back in a relationship.
我要发短信给安迪
I'm going to text Andy.
我就知道 我早说中 我早约中了
I knew it. I called that. I booty called that.
你的约炮资格证被取消了
Your casual sex card is being revoked.
很遗憾的是 安迪还是个活跃会员呢
Unfortunately, Andy is still an active member.
-十分活跃 -你这是什么意思
- Very active. -What are you talking about?
他有"根"很活跃的"会员"
I'm saying he has an active member.
他说他有跟别人有交往
He told me he's seeing someone.
他在跟人交往吗
He's seeing someone?
其实 还"交"了不只几个人呢
Actually, he's seeing a few someones.
多少个人啊
How many someones?
感觉又来了
Oh, it's back.
你觉得这瘙痒跟
Do you think this itch has anything to do
他那"几个人"有关吗
with those many someones?
会不会是他传染了什么病给我啊
Do you think he gave me something?
如果他真传染给你 那你也传染给这柜台了
Well, if he did, you just gave it to the counter.
穷人在有线上医生网前都怎么过的啊
What did poor people do before WebMD?
病了就死了呗
They died.
靠 那是什么啊
Ooh! What is that?
红红稠稠的 希望你别中了这个啊
It's all red and chunky. I hope that's not what you have.
麦克斯 那是你的莎莎酱
Max, that's salsa.
-但你看 -哇 这又他妈是啥啊
- But look. - Oh! What the hell is that?
新罗谢尔市的珍得的是啥鬼玩意啊
What the hell does Jen from New Rochelle have?
只是皮疹 珍说
It's a rash. Jen says
"有段时间挺糟的 后来又消失了"
"It was bad for awhile, then disappeared."
所以珍的病 基本就是"我老爸"嘛
So Jen came down with a case of "My father"?
皮疹而已 感觉还好啊
A rash. That doesn't sound so bad.
我可以接受皮疹
I could live with a rash.
但网上医生认为是疱疹呢
Except Dr. Web thinks it might be herpes.
相信我 我没得那个
Trust me, I don't have it.
这珍一看就是个骚货
Jen's obviously a whore.
那你那里看起来像这样吗
Well, does it look like this?
不知道啊 我没这么柔软可以自己弯腰看到
I don't know, I can't quite bend over far enough to see it.
好吧 那我帮你看
Fine. I'll look at it.
什么 不行
What? No!
有何不可 珍都让我看她的了
What? Jen showed me hers.
我肯定我只是得了个皮疹
I'm sure mine is just a rash.
科罗拉多的凯西说
Cathy from Colorado says,
"我以为只是个皮疹 结果呢
"I thought it was just a rash, but guess what?
皮疹永远都是疱疹"
Rashes are always herpes."
我不能得疱疹
I can't have herpes.
性爱是穷人唯一玩得起的娱乐了
Sex is the only fun thing poor people can afford.
天啊 神啊 菩萨啊 观音啊
Oh, my God. Oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God.
就让我帮你看嘛
Just let me see it.
麦克斯 让你看 那我就没脸住下去了
Max, I could not continue to live here if you ever saw it.
那我绝对要看了
Well, then definitely let me see it.
怕啥啊 你有的我都有
It's okay, I have one too,
除了我的那里有个"欢迎进入"的脚踏垫
except mine has a "Welcome" mat.
我知道了 我拍张那里的照片就行了
I know, I'll just take a picture of it.
这就是金·卡戴珊出名的原因
And that's how Kim Kardashian became famous.
拍我"小妹妹"的照已经够惨了
It's bad enough I'm taking a picture of my vagina,
更惨的是我还得用Iphone 3来拍
I'm doing it with an Iphone 3.
太暗了 要闪光灯
Too dark. Needs a flash.
行 但注意红眼啊
All right, but watch out for red-eye.
这下瞧见她了
Ohh...There she is.
看样子绝对有问题
Yeah, that's definitely something.
-让我看看 -等等 这得加个滤镜
- Let me see it. - Wait, it needs a filter.
低保真度 巴伦西亚滤镜 都不要
Lo-fi, no. Valencia, no.
-还是加个边框啊 -快给我看
- Oh, maybe just a border. - Just give it to me.
哎哟 这绝对有问题
Oh ho, that's not good.
我就想声明一下
I just want to go on the record.
她平常不是这样的
It doesn't always look like that.
平常还挺美的呢
It's actually quite pretty.
现在她则是丑得很有个性
Well, now it has a good personality.
估计是疾病管理局的人来敲门
Oh, that's probably the center for disease control
开着隔离车要把我带走了
coming to get me with their van.
我去开吧 走路时舒服点
I'll get it. The walking helps.
我的老天啊
Oh, my God.
神啊 菩萨啊 观音啊 亲娘啊
Oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God.
姑娘们 我打包了中餐
Hi, girls! I got chinese food.
要不要一起玩啊
You want to hang out?
苏菲 现在不是时候
Sophie, this isn't a good time.
惨了 有人在走疱疹步
Uh-ohh, someone's got the herp walk.
苏菲 还不知道是什么病呢
Sophie, we don't know what it is.
可能只是个皮疹而已
It could just be a rash.
的确有可能 不过基本不会的
Yeah, it could, but it probably isn't.
-来 让我看看 -住手
- Yeah, let me see. - Stop it.
干嘛 没事的 我以前在波兰是个护士呢
What? It's okay, I was a nurse back in Poland.
你听说过"无国界医生"吗
You've heard of "Doctors without borders"?
我当年则是"无执照护士"
Well, we were "Nurses without credentials."
我们当年的口号是"干嘛 我们就想帮忙嘛"
Yeah. Our motto was: "What? We want to help."
不 不许
Quit--stop it!
麦克斯 不准给苏菲看...
Max, don't show Sophie--
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
拜托哦 你好歹也给这图上个滤镜吧
Oh, I mean, come on, slap a filter on this thing.
好了 我受够了
Okay. I'm done.
我受够无执照护士
I'm done with nurses without credentials
也受够远端线上医生了
Or doctors without faces.
明天 我要去免费诊所
Tomorrow, I'm going to a free clinic.
你真的挺严重的
Well, is real bad.
你最好跑着去 别走疱疹步了
You better run, don't herp walk.
这上面说平均每六个人就会有一个得疱疹
Whoa, this thing says one out of six people have herpes!
麦克斯 这里任何人都可能是那"六分之一"
Max, anyone in here could be the "one in six."
既然我们都来了 你不顺便测一下吗
Are you sure you don't want to get tested while we're here?
不了 我任何测试成绩都很烂
Nah, I'm bad at tests.
再说了 如果花不起钱看医生
Besides, if you can't afford a doctor,
那你最好把所有钱花在大麻上
it's better to just spend whatever money you got on weed
这样有助于让你忘记病痛
to help you forget whatever you got.
卡洛琳·钱宁
Caroline Channing.
太尴尬了
That's so embarrassing.
她还能再大声点叫我名字吗
Could she say my name any louder?
卡洛琳·钱宁
Caroline Channing!
-看来她能 -钱宁小姐
- I guess she could. - Miss channing,
你这里写来看病的原因是
now, you wrote here the reason for your visit
"私处有不舒服的感觉"
is an "uncomfortable sensation in your nether regions."
你能说得更详细点吗
Could you be more specific?
我们能去更私密处
Is there a more private area
讨论我的私密处吗
we could discuss my private area?
真是抱歉
Oh, I'm sorry!
让我把我的热气球拿出来
Let me bring out my hot air balloon
我们边来一趟环市之旅
and we'll take a tour of the city...
边讨论你不舒服的女人"位"
while we discuss your uncomfortable lady sensation.
雪莉 我觉得这办公室
Shirley, the only lady sensation
唯一有女人"味"的就是你
I'm seeing in this office is you.
谢谢夸奖 妹子
Oh, well, I appreciate that, girl.
我试着用幽默感减轻工作负担
I try to lighten the load with a little humor.
我不需要你的冷笑话 谢谢
Well, I don't need the jokes. Thank you.
笑话不是说给你听的 是我们自娱自乐的
Oh, they not for you. They for us.
我是来做疱疹测试的
I need to be tested for... herpes.
你的声音听起来就像在做疱疹香水广告
Girl, you sound like you're doing a perfume ad for herpes.
把手机拿给她看
Just give her the phone.
这要么是疱疹
Well, this is either herpes
要么就是我没见过的怪病
or something I ain't never seen before.
单纯疱疹病毒2型不属于普通标准检测
Now, the HSV-2 is not a standard pap.
这是专门的血液检测 需要250块
It is a specific blood test, and it is $250.
我知道能在接下来一小时挣到钱的
Well, the only way I know how to get money for that test
唯一办法会让我染上性病
in the next hour will probably give me an STD.
或许我们可以讲讲价便宜点
Can we maybe work out a cheaper price?
我们是附近威廉斯堡餐厅的服务员
We're waitresses nearby at the Williamsburg diner.
只要我在那上班一天 你来吃饭都不要钱
I can give you free food for as long as I work there.
如今我可能得这种病 我还能有什么出路
And now that I may have this, I mean, where else am I going?
验血还是否认
Blood test or denial?
验血
Blood test.
我去管安迪借钱好了
I'll just ask Andy for a loan.
但这其实是照价赔偿
But it's actually more of a buy,
因为他毁坏了物业
since he already ruined the property.
经典的"损坏了就要赔偿"
Classic "you break it, you buy it."
麦克斯
Hey, Max.
很高兴见到你
Good to see you.
我跟这男的搞过一次
I hooked up with that guy once.
你知道他是来这是看什么病
Um, do you know what he was here for
得病了多久吗
and how long he's had it?
算了 给我个过往性史表格吧
You know what, give me one of those sexual history forms.
这个性史名单太难填了
This sexual history list is hard.
不能直接选个前十名吗
Can't it just be a top ten?
安迪还没来
Well, Andy's not here yet.
他可能忙着周旋于
He's probably busy getting busy
他那帮下贱反社会骚货吧
with his ragtag team of gutter skanks.
"下贱反社会骚货"
"Gutter skanks"?
她们不是最爱死亡金属乐队吗
Didn't I see them open for Cannibal Corpse?
你要放轻松
Look, you need to relax.
我们何不喝一杯 或连喝九杯
Why don't we just get a drink, or nine?
两杯双份的杰克姜味鸡尾酒
Two double Jack and Gingers.
对了 杰克 第38位
Oh, yeah, Jack. Number 38.
还有那位姜色头发男 第39位
Oh, and that ginger. Number 39.
麦克斯 瞧 新罗谢尔市的珍
Max, look, Jen from New Rochelle
在线上医生网站上更新状态了
put up a new update on WebMD.
她说在加入一个叫做"疱男疹女"网站后
She says her life has gotten so much better
她的人生比以前好多了
after joining a site called "His-and-herpes."
安迪 请坐
Hi, Andy. Have a seat.
记住 你不知道是不是他传给你的
Remember, you don't know that he gave it to you,
你也不知道你是否中招了 所以要淡定
and you don't know that you have it, so be cool.
别担心 麦克斯 我有分寸
Don't worry, Max, I got this.
安迪 我得病了
And Andy, I got that!
我曾经认为
I thought it was annoying
人们拍下自己的食物挺讨人厌的
when people took pictures of their food.
你打算什么时候跟我说实话 安迪
When were you gonna tell me, Andy?
要等我的阴道瘙痒炙热
When my vagina burst into flames
转成怒火燎原的"森林"大火时吗
and became an actual burning bush?
慢着 那是你那里吗
Wait, that's yours?
史上最烂的自拍照 对吗
Worst selfie ever, right?
我完全认不出来
Wow, I didn't recognize it.
是不是被太阳晒焦了
Was it out in the sun?
你欠我验血费250块 安迪
You owe me $250 for the blood test, Andy.
还有9块钱酒钱
And $9 for that drink.
你们俩先冷静下来
Look, everybody just calm down.
安迪 你可能有或没有传染疱疹给她
Andy, you may or may not have given her herpes.
她可能有或没有反应过度
She may or may not be overreacting.
我可能有或没有睡过那位酒保
I may or may not have slept with that bartender.
他虽然是我喜欢的型
He is my type,
但他现在还有工作 所以应该没有
and yet, he has a job, so he's not,
那就把他归为"可能"那一类
and he goes in the "Maybes."
卡洛琳 真的很抱歉
Look, Caroline, I'm really sorry,
但我干净得很
but I am totally clean.
分手之后 我只跟两个女人发生过安全性行为
Since we broke up, I have only had safe sex
一个是专科教师 一位是牙科清洁师
with a special ed teacher and a dental hygienist.
她的工作名都有着"清洁"两个字了
I mean, that job has "hygiene" right in the title.
等等 是有那么几次
Wait, oh, there were a couple of times
我跟我的手有过危险性行为
where I did have unsafe sex with myself.
但只有在我睡不着的时候
But only when I couldn't sleep.
以及其他很多时候
And a lot of other times.
我明天就去做检测
I will go get tested tomorrow,
但拜托 与此同时
but please, in the meantime,
不要总往最坏的情况想
try not to go to the worst-case scenario.
我没有往最坏的情况想
I'm not going to the worst-case scenario,
但如果咱俩都中招了 那没人会要咱俩了
but if we both have it, no one else is going to want us,
那我们只好结婚了
so we should just get married.
"你若传我疱疹 我必生死相依"
"You gave me herpes, now you have to marry me."
你想把这句金言当成我们的结婚誓词吗
You want to save that gold for our wedding vows?
如果你们不用 那给我用吧
Well, if you don't use it, I will.
我现在就想知道测试结果 等不到明天了
I can't wait till tomorrow for my test results.
我要打电话给诊所
I'm going to call the clinic.
你都留了10通留言了
You've left, like, ten messages.
你就像诊所的疯狂前女友
You're acting like the clinic's crazy ex-girlfriend.
我要再留一通留言
Well, I'm leaving another message.
把我手机给我
Hand me my phone.
干嘛
What?
万一你真中招了 我可不能病倒
I have to stay healthy in case you have it.
总得有人去帮你领福利救济金吧
Someone's got to pick up your welfare checks.
这就是我现在的人生
Well, this is my life now.
身染疱疹 在一家不入流的餐馆工作
Working at a diner with herpes.
我仅剩的最大希望就是
The very best I can ever hope to be
当一位身染疱疹的年轻姑娘的良师益友
is a mentor for a younger girl with herpes.
你好 或许你可以帮我
Hi. Maybe you can help me.
你的笑容配上我有病的心脏
Well, with that smile and my bad heart,
我会拼死帮你的
I'll die trying.
我是来找在这家餐厅工作的
I'm looking for the overly-emotional girl
一位过度情绪化的女服务员
that works here as a waitress.
天啊 你来这里干什么
Oh, my god! What are you doing here?
我要死了吗 你是带我走的死神吗
Am I dying? Are you the angel of death?
我找到她了
I think I found her.
我们能坐下来聊一句吗
Can we have a seat for a minute?
麦克斯 她要坐下来谈
Max, Max, she wants to sit down.
快过来拉住我的手
Come here and hold my hand.
等知道结果后 我会拉住你的手的
Oh, I'll hold your hand after I find out what you have.
没必要这么小题大作
No need to be all dramatic.
我是来告诉你 你的验血结果出来了
I just came to tell you that your blood test came back,
但我不能在没有医生的情况下透露结果
But I am not allowed to give you the results without a doctor.
-不可以吗 -不可以
- You're not? - No, I am not.
绝对是不行不行[阴性 阴性]
That's a neg-a-tive, a neg-a-tive.
等等 你是说我没有得吗
Wait. Are you saying it's negative?
我可没有这么说
I could not tell you that.
我也不能告诉你不舒服可能是
I also could not tell you that it was probably
因为对肥皂或对洗衣粉过敏
an allergic reaction to soap or laundry detergent.
天啊 麦克斯 罪魁祸首是
Oh, my god! Max, it was that fabric softener ball
不到一元店的衣物柔顺球
from the "Under a dollar" Store.
我不是个廉价的妓女 我只是个穷鬼
I'm not a cheap whore. I'm just poor.
雪莉 你人真好 还特意过来一趟
Shirley, it was really cool of you to come all the way in,
因为我们刚才真的很沮丧
because we were really very upset,
沮丧到像你这么专业有爱的医务人员
so upset that a caring medical professional like you
很可能会给予我们某物[大麻]
would probably help us out
来缓解我们的焦虑 或让我们派对更尽兴
with something for our anxiety or parties.
想得美
Nice try.
但我来这里不是因为我心肠好
But I'm not here just out of the goodness of my heart.
我是来这里吃免费的薯条的
I'm here for my free fries.
我快饿死了
I'm starving.
自从看了你手机那张惨不忍睹的照片后
I haven't been able to eat since you showed me
我就没胃口吃过东西
that phone picture of your bits and pieces.
-薯条马上来 -真是太谢谢你了
- Fries coming right up. - And thank you so much.
给人们传递好消息的感觉真不错
Oh, it's nice to give out good news.
你呢 我何时能给你带去好消息
What about you? When can I give you some good news?
我明天就去 我在等
I'll be in tomorrow, I'm just waiting
约翰·梅尔回我的电话
for a call back from John Mayer.
你好 我来找李憨
Hi, I'm looking for Han Lee.
那是我要介绍给阿憨的女孩
Oh, that's the girl I set up Han with.
看不见有喉结 你可以上了
No visible adam's apple. Go for it.
麦克斯 她很漂亮
Oh, Max, she's very pretty.
你确定她会喜欢我吗
Are you sure she'll go for me?
我觉得有可能哦 过去打个招呼吧
I think she might. Let's go say hi.
你是珍吧 这位就是李憨
Hi, you must be Jen. Jen, this is Han.
阿憨 这位是新罗谢尔市的珍
Han, this is Jen from New Rochelle.
-你好 -你好
- Hi. - Hello.
-新罗谢尔市的珍 不是吧 -怎么了
- Jen from New Rochelle? Max, no! - What?
她也可能只是对洗衣粉过敏而已啊
It could just be a reaction to her laundry detergent.
我没病 干净得很
I'm clean! Totally clean!
雪莉跟我一样惊讶呢
Shirley was as surprised as I am.
麦克斯 我真为你开心
Oh, Max, I'm so happy for you.
对啊 我躲过这一劫 但从今开始
Yep, I dodged a bullet, but from now on,
我要变得更加小心谨慎
I'm going to be a little more discerning.
我不是13岁的花痴妹了
I'm not 13 anymore.
我刚发短信告诉安迪 这是虚惊一场
So I just texted Andy and told him it was a false alarm.
-我没有中招 -他怎么说
- I didn't have it. - What did he say?
他说"你还醒着呢"
He said, "hey, you up?"
但我肯定不会去他家的
But I'm definitely not gonna go.
我会吗
Am I?
好吧 我就直说吧
All right, here's the thing.
这件事比安迪还重大
This is about something bigger than Andy.
-其实安迪蛮大... -我知道
- Actually, Andy's quite-- - Oh, I know.
我出来喝杯水
Came out to get a drink of water.
不小心看见 爱死了
Saw it, loved it.
我就长话短说吧
Look, I'm going to keep this simple.
你在利用安迪来填满你的空洞
You are using Andy to fill a hole.
是啊 麦克斯 做爱不就是这样吗
Yes, Max, that's how sex works.
自从小蛋糕店倒闭后
Ever since the business closed,
你多出了很多空余时间
you've got all this free time,
你不知道自己该干些什么
and you don't know what to do with yourself.
我懂你的意思
I hear you.
你说得对 自从小蛋糕店倒闭后
You're right, ever since the business closed,
-我的确有个大洞 -我知道
- I do have a huge hole. - I know.
出来喝水
Came out to get a drink of water.
不小心看见 爱死了
Saw it, loved it.
麦克斯 我知道我们曾说过
Max, I know we said we were gonna
总有一天会东山再起
do the cupcake business again,
但现在我们必须要付诸行动
but now we have to make it real.
我是个商业女强人
I mean, I'm a businesswoman.
我得开店做生意 否则
I need to have a business, or apparently,
我会让别人的"生意"来入侵我的"店面"
I'm gonna put someone else's business into my business.
麦克斯 明天我们就开工
So Max, tomorrow, we start again,
这一次 我们一定要全力以赴
and this time, we have to give it our all.
洁净私处 全心全意 十拿九稳
Clear vaginas, full hearts, can't lose.
姑娘们
Hey, girls.
我特意下来告诉你
I came down with a solution
我想到解决你疱疹的问题了 卡洛琳
to your herpes problem, Caroline.
千万不要告诉任何人
Just don't tell anyone!
-苏菲 我没有疱疹 -就是这样
- Sophie, I don't have it. - That's it!
坚决抵死不认
That's the way to do it!
问题解决 好啦 再见啦
Problem solved. All right, bye-bye.